

## CONTACT

0311-7871231



Rawalpindi, Pakistan



ereeqatoheed@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ereeqa-t-

6b764618b/

## **SKILLS**

Content Writer



Digital Marketer

Community Manager

Creative Thinker

## **EDUCATION**

**Bachelors in Artificial Intelligence** 

Air University | 2020-2024 Islamabad, Pakistan

Intermediate in Computer Science

Roots International College | 2018-2020 Rawalpindi, Pakistan

## **EREEQA TOHEED**

## **ABOUT ME**

Diligent and hard-working, my experience as a content writer and social media marketer has allowed me to develop a strong foundation of interpersonal skills, which I continue to build on during the everyday grind. I'm a dedicated team player but have no issues delegating tasks. In addition to my education and work experience, I am a driven individual with an entrepreneurial spirit.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Junior Content Writer**

Imperial MEA

January 2023- Present

Skills: Blog Writing · Web Content Writing · Search Engine Optimization (SEO) · TextMetrics Optimization . Uber Suggest

#### **Team Lead Social Media Marketing**

**Project C Foundation** 

January 2023- Present

Skills: Leadership Project Management Team Management

#### Intern Social Media Marketing

Project C Foundation

September 2022- January 2023

**Skills:** Digital Marketing · Social Media · Social

Media Marketing

#### Social Media Manager

Vectragi

October 2022- Feburary 2023

Skills: Digital Marketing - Social Media Management · Social Media Marketing



## CONTACT

69

0311-7871231



Rawalpindi, Pakistan



ereeqatoheed@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ereeqa-t-

6b764618b/

## **SKILLS**

Content Writer



O Digital Marketer

O Community Manager

Creative Thinker

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelors in Artificial Intelligence Air University | 2020-2024 Islamabad, Pakistan

Intermediate in Computer Science
Roots International College | 2018-2020
Rawalpindi, Pakistan

# **EREEQA TOHEED**

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Content Writer**

Miracle Solutions LLC September 2022- October 2022

Skills: Blog Writing · Web Content Writing ·

#### **Content Writer**

Webx E-commerce

June 2022 - September 2022

**Skills:** Blog Writing · Web Content Writing · Search Engine Optimization (SEO) · Article Writing

whiling

#### **Freelance News Writer**

Writtech

September 2021 - November 2021

**Skills:** Technical Writing · News Writing · Article

Writing

#### **Computer Science Tutor**

Lipson Academy

August 2019 - October 2019

**Skills:** Management, Time Management.

Organisation

## **PROJECTS**

Emotion Detection System

Arduino Based Smart House System

Grade Detection System

Restaurant Management System